bigsellingoptins.com 2014-06-25

# 

IMPORTANT! THIS PRIVACY POLICY (“POLICY”) DESCRIBES LISTERUPTION.COM, INCORPORATED PROTECTS, USES AND SHARES ANY INFORMATION WHICH IS PROVIDED BY YOU. BY ACCESSING THE SITE, YOU ARE INDICATING THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTOOD AND AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLCY AND OUR TERMS OF SERVICE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF SERVICE OR OUR PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITE OR ANY SERVICES OFFERED AT THE SITE.

ListEruption.com strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internet

technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may

use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street

address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. We will

never sell, barter, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party.

Period.”

**How we gather information from users**

How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the

activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For

example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access

to certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as newsletters or

when you make a purchase. You may provide information when you participate

in sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other

interactive areas of our site. Like most Web sites, ListEruption.com also collects

information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be

transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet

Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information

from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and

password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you

visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular

advertisement while visiting our site. As we adopt additional technology, we may

also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose

not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse

to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of

the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may

not be able to customize the site’s features according to your preferences.

**What we do with the information we collect**

Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and

deliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and

do not share your information with anyone.

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may

be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your

usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help

enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or

what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may occasionally be

shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does

not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to

identify you individually.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on ListEruption.com to

communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences;

our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by

ListEruption.com and other topics we think you might find of interest.

Personally Identifiable Information collected by ListEruption.com may also be

used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration,

troubleshooting, processing of ecommerce transactions, administration of

sweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you. Certain third

parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web

hosting service for example) may access such information. We will use your

information only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we

continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other

companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among

the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a

court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so

by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to

law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary.

Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

**Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements**

ListEruption.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the

privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our

partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through

our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices.

For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a

frame on a ListEruption.com page, certain content that is actually created or

hosted by a third party. Also, through ListEruption.com you may be introduced to,

or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes

offered by other parties. ListEruption.com is not responsible for the actions or

policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of

those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a

third party.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may

use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences

or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served

by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine

whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Other features

available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use

cookies or other technology to gather information. ListEruption.com does not

control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and

is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable

Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed

publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge

and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties.

Such activities are beyond the control of ListEruption.com and this policy.

**Children**

ListEruption.com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable

Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we

discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of

this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe

ListEruption.com has any information from or about anyone under 13, please

contact us at the address listed below.

**Contacting Us**

We can be reached by contacting:

ListEruption.com

Email: support(at)ListEruption.com

**Changes to this Policy**

ListEruption.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please

check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following

the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used

according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was

collected.

**Governing Law**

This policy and the use of this Site are governed by North Carolina law. If a dispute

arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a

mutually agreed-upon mediator in the following location: North Carolina. Any costs

and fees other than attorney fees associated with the mediation will be shared

equally by each of us.

If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through

mediation, we agree to submit the dispute to binding arbitration at the following

location: North Carolina, under the rules of the American Arbitration Association.

Judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitration may be entered in any

court with jurisdiction to do so. ListEruption.com is controlled, operated and

administered entirely within North Carolina. This statement and the policies outlined

herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights

in or on behalf of any party.

**Email Privacy**

Our privacy policy keeps your email safe and secure. We will never sell rent, give, or

divulge your email information to ANYONE
